From the headlines to the front lines.
Whiskey Tango Foxtrot is a comedy, drama, war film directed by Glenn Ficarra.
In 2002, cable news producer Kim Barker decides to shake up her routine
by taking a daring new assignment in Kabul, Afghanistan.
Dislodged from her comfortable American lifestyle, Barker finds
herself in the middle of an out-of-control war zone.
Luckily, she meets Tanya Vanderpoel, a fellow journalist who
takes the shell-shocked reporter under her wing.
Amid the militants, warlords and nighttime partying, Barker
discovers the key to becoming a successful correspondent.
Kim Barker, played by Tina Fey.
Tanya Vanderpoel, played by Margot Robbie.
General Hollanek, played by Billy Bob Thornton.
Iain MacKelpie, played by Martin Freeman.
Chris, played by Josh Charles.
Ali Massoud Sadiq, played by Alfred Molina.
Whiskey Tango Foxtrot is a 2016 American biographical war comedy-drama film,
directed by Glenn Ficarra and John Requa and written by Robert Carlock.
Based on the memoir The Taliban Shuffle: Strange Days in Afghanistan and Pakistan by Kim Barker,
the adaptation's title spells WTF in the military standard NATO phonetic alphabet.
The film stars Tina Fey, Margot Robbie, Martin Freeman, Alfred Molina, and Billy Bob
Thornton and was released on March 4, 2016, by Paramount Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the acting but criticized the predictable
screenplay and execution, and grossed $24 million against its $35 million budget.
The film explores themes of rescue, journalist, based on
novel or book, kidnapping, journalism.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.